Please contact turkision@gmail.com
for any inquiries
NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING THE FILMING
OF THIS PRODUCTION
He who dies ends up under the dark soil…
…and I am ready to take this sacred
burden.
Allahu Akbar!
You.
What kind of a devil are you?
Just like you they have nine lives.
Osman Bey.
My Allah…
…from the mischief of my enemies...
...I take refuge behind your greatness.
My Bey!
With the name of Allah!
What are you waiting for?
Catch him!
Inform the soldiers immediately and
order them to blockade the forest.
They shall take the corpses of Balgay
and Cerkutay to Geyhatu.
Let them say...
...Princess Sofia took care of Osman.
Boran.
Let's split!
As you wish my Bey.
I will find you.
Go now.
Do you want to be my daughter, Aygül?
They arranged the wedding in a hurry!
They made a vow of sheep and ram, of
horse and stud...
...without thinking for a second!
They created sorrow out of a fresh bride!
Sorrow!
Set me free!
-Please stop, Aygul. Stop!
-Set me free!
Set me free!
-Please relax.
-Set me free!
Set me free!
Calm down!
Aygül Hanım, please.
-My Aygül, please stop.
-Set me free!
Set me free!
Aygül!
Please stop and take a few bites.
I don't want to!
Aygül!
Then you will rest for a while, huh?
They tied me!
They should tie her, not me!
I brought you soup, Aygül.
Please, you should eat something.
I don’t want to!
My Aygül.
Do you want to play a game together?
Be my baby and I will feed you.
Huh?
Come on.
Take a seat.
My dear rose.
Let’s get our tummy full.
My beautiful baby.
Go on my beautiful baby.
How wonderful!
Go on my beautiful daughter.
How magnificent my rose is!
How magnificent, indeed!
Just a little bit more patience.
I am coming, my Bey.
I am coming.
Göktuğ!
Boran?
Come here my brother.
Where is Osman Bey?
Where did they take him?
Göktuğ, lie down my brother.
Come on!
Bamsı Bey!
My Boran and Göktuğ.
Are you okay?
We are okay, my Bey.
Where is my Osman?
He is running away from
Sofia’s soldiers, my Bey.
There are too many of them.
I don’t have another child to lose.
Göktuğ, may you endure it, my child.
Bamsı Bey.
I can endure...
...but my brother…
…he is okay, right?
Let’s see how thick your skins are.
This way!
Hurry up!
Come to me!
Come to me with your living deads.
I will show you where I am headed.
Go to this way!
Block the path!
My child.
Allah knows the truth behind everything.
Your brother is laying sick at the Tent’s
dispensary.
He will get better with the help of Allah.
What have I done to my brother?
If something happens to my brother…
...I can’t live, Bamsı Bey!
What are you doing?
What do you think you are doing?
How would you explain this to Allah?
Don’t you dare!
From now on, being alive is illicit to
me, Bamsı Bey.
My child if you take your own life now…
…what is going to happen to your
brother’s will?
I neither have lots of gold nor goods
and land.
The only thing I can leave to you
is my loyalty to Osman Bey.
May you be an Alp to Osman Bey.
My blood and my life are yours, Osman Bey.
You are free to ask for the head of that
Balgay dog.
Just like you are free to take my head.
The choice is yours.
My life is a sacrifice on your path.
What’s going to happen to those promises
you made to your brother and Osman?
Do you want the Tyrant get away with
everything?
Now, either stand up and fulfill your
promises…
…or take your own life by contradicting
Allah’s words.
Thanks to Allah, she attacked me, my Bey.
What if she had chosen to hurt herself?
Hopefully, this will be the last time.
I just hope that your heart does not
become darkened…
…and narrowed.
Since I am located there…
…when your heart gets darkened…
…so do I.
This is the reason.
Don’t be sad.
I beg you, please don’t be sad.
In this life…
…my fortune got better only with your
presence.
I did not know your value for
years, Hazal.
Everything would have been different if we
were together since the beginning.
You would have taken care after me.
And I would not have turned out like this
in the end.
Maybe it was Allah’s will to come
together now.
The past is past.
We are one and together from now on.
I will always support you with
my prayers, love, and everything, my Bey.
We will fight against everything together.
Just like we will deal with everything.
Yes, we will deal with everything
together, my Hazal.
Together.
May Allah never take us apart.
Amin.
What now?
You have nowhere to run, Osman Bey.
They killed my father in Constantinopolis
because of you.
I made a promise to my father
before he died.
Today, I am going to fulfil
his last wish.
Such a dutiful child you are, Sofia.
His last wish was to bury you under
the very lands you took away from us.
This dutiful child is going to do
what she promised.
You lost, Sofia!
I spoiled both of your games!
Both Subutay and Balgay could not
fight against us.
Geyhatu is not going to be an exception.
You will never take back the lands
my father conquered.
We never lose, Osman.
Thanks to you, we formed an alliance
with Geyhatu.
I got stronger because of this.
I am going to create
a new order with Monks.
Eventually, I will sit on
my rightful throne.
You are dead, now.
Catch him!
With the name of Allah!
I wish we found a cure for my Aygul.
My own child is chained down.
How can a father’s heart bare this pain?
I have a cure in mind.
However, I’m not sure if you will like it.
Tell me, Hatun!
What is it? Tell me!
If there is a cure I will
bring it from Baghdad.
Our Aygul’s cure is not that far away.
It’s very close.
What are you talking about, Hatun?
My Dündar...
My Bey...
Let’s send our Aygul to Kastamonu.
Near our Tent, in Seydihan,
there are famous physicians.
Many people go there
to find cures for unknown diseases.
The air and water
there are very different.
Unlike this place which
is a burned down Tent.
Wars, raids, martyrs.
What do we have except Bala?
And she can not be
sufficient for everyone.
I don't think we'll find any cures
for our child here.
Our Aygül needs fresh air, Bey.
How can she find that air in this Tent?
She'll be very comfortable there.
She'll be protected and looked after.
I don't know if you have
anything better in mind.
you're right, Hatun.
Our troubles are enough for us.
The girl will be wasted here,
you're right.
A beautiful girl will go to waste.
Okay. We shall send here immediately.
Even your words refreshed me.
This will be good for my Aygül.
With Allah's help.
My Osman! Oh my!
Are you okay?
What do you mean
Aygül attacked you, mother?
She's crazy, son.
She's out of her mind.
Anyway. I'll send her to the physicians
near my brother.
Tell me what my brother said.
Geyhatu comes like a flood
and burns like fire, he said.
He doesn't want any trouble
in Söğüt or Kayı Tent.
- Sensitive times, mother.
- We know that!
What are his orders? Tell me that!
He'll calm Geyhatu down so that he doesn't
slaughter all the Turks around here.
He'll do everything necessary.
But...
He wants us to stop Osman from acting mad.
Osman fell into Sofia's trap.
He's done.
The bad news will be here before sunset.
Let's see. Because my aunt is watching
the Tent.
He doesn't want any Muslim blood to spill
because of a mad young man.
He wants to know everything.
He emphasised. Hazal Hatun
should prepare Dündar, he said.
This is now our time.
Sofia!
Protect the Princess!
Come on, my valiant!
Don't let them get away!
To the horses!
Quick!
My Aygül...
My gracious daughter.
I realised what I've done to you
too late.
My insides hurt every time I see you.
I can't stand it.
But I found a solution. There are famous
physicians in Kastamonu Seyidiyan.
You'll go there and come back
as my Aygül, with Allah's help.
These lands are harsh, my daughter.
Let alone breathing, even staying
alive is a matter of luck.
What do you say, daughter?
Do you want to go?
This is the best way.
I'll harden my heart
and you'll return to the Tent recovered.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim
You called me, Hazal Hatun.
Are you hungry, my lion?
Excuse me, Hazal Hatun.
How could I dine on your table?
We thought you were our son.
Have a seat.
Do as I say.
You asked to be an Alp and
I sent you to practice.
You asked for friendship and
I put you on Dündar's side.
I'm basically a mother to you, son.
Now I expect you to return
the favour as a child.
I'll do as you order, Hazal Hatun.
I don't like to beat around the bush.
You know what Aygül has done to me.
I've heard. I'm sorry.
Thank you. You also know what happens
to those who try to take my life.
Aygül will be setting off.
And you'll go with her.
You'll do what's necessary...
Vultures will get her dead body.
If he hears about it,
Dündar Bey will end my bloodline.
She's out of her mind, Hazal Hatun.
That what I'm saying.
She's out of her mind.
If she was to fell from somewhere,
Allah forbid...
If she was to throw herself from a cliff,
who could hold you responsible?
If he finds out that you killed Aygül...
... Dündar will kill you.
If you can't kill Aygül...
... I will make you beg for death.
I called you my lion.
Act like one!
No need to be a hare.
As you order, Hazal Hatun.
They're gone.
- We'll keep searching.
- Osman is a master predator.
Finding him in a forest
is almost impossible.
He's badly hurt.
We can't get such an opportunity again.
We won't find him if we give up now.
Kayı's borders are from this
point forward. We might fall into a trap.
I was never this close to killing him.
You're right. But the state
of our soldiers isn't good.
Don't be stubborn.
We should go back to the castle.
This is just the beginning, Osman.
These lands will be your grave.
We're going back to the castle.
Let's go.
Oh, Osman!
Oh, my valiant.
Son...
We need to sear your wound. But
we can't light fires, Sofia is after us.
We need to go to the Tent
as soon as possible.
What's up with him?
About his brother.
It seems that the mistake
he made curses him.
What are you doing, my Osman?
You should rest!
Oh, Osman!
Osman Bey...
What have I done?
You killed Balgay...
... who tried to make you
kill your brother with spells.
But neither oppression nor tyrants
have come to an end.
We need to stand still.
We need to stay alert.
Stay with me at all times...
... so that we can end
the oppression and the tyrants.
We can end--
My Osman!
My valiant!
My Osman! Hold on!
We'll get to the Tent!
Boran!
Let's go.
I'm here, daughter!
Call me and I'll come flying to you!
The fire inside you will be gone.
The storms in your heart will calm down.
You'll return recovered,
with Allah's help.
It will be over. Don't worry.
Of course it will, my child.
It will be over.
We'll spend beautiful days together once
you recover and come back to the Tent.
Aygül...
My daughter...
My beautiful daughter...
Remember what I've told you. As you have
a father here, you also have a mother.
You're my child too.
You're my life.
You're in my prayers.
May Allah protect you.
It won't take long, my daughter.
I'll visit you.
I'll bring you good news from the Tent.
It won't take long.
My Aygül... This will be
our last separation, hopefully.
Then your father
will always keep you close.
Always.
Come on.
Goodbye, my daughter.
Make it tighter.
- You do the printing.
- Okay.
- May Allah help you!
- Good luck!
May Allah protect you, my daughter.
Aygül!
Where is she going?
Keep working.
I'll be right back.
Dündar Bey! I saw Aygül.
Where is she going?
To find a cure.
It's for good, Hatun, don't worry.
What are you talking about?
Where is my little one's cure?
In Kastamonu. She'll stay
in a dispensary...
... near my brother Yavlak Hasan's
Tent in Seydihan.
There, she'll be protected
and looked after, hopefully.
Hazal... You keep talking about
Yavlak Hasan since you came here.
What are you talking about, Selcan Hatun?
When did she do wrong?
We all owe our lives to her.
Remember, Dündar Bey.
We owe our life to Allah,
and our home to Süleyman Şah!
Why are you sending her to Kastamonu for
a cure? Did Söğüt run out of physicians?
Why are we here for?
You're like a mother.
So I know why you worry, Selcan Hatun.
But change is good.
How can she heal with everything
happening around here?
My heart is already burning.
Please don't push me.
We lost my valiant
Batur because of your thoughtlessness.
Now listen carefully, Dündar.
If something happens to my Aygül...
... then I'll be a burden to you.
Quick!
Clear the way!
- Clear the way!
Clear!
Clear the way!
Osman!
Is he alive, Bamsı Bey?
Tell me that he's alive!
He's alive. But he's badly hurt!
We need to take care of it!
- Where is Selcan Hatun? Selcan Hatun!
- Osman!
Where is Selcan Hatun?!
- Get out of the way! Osman!
- Selcan Hatun!
- Hold on, Osman!
- My nephew! Osman!
- Osman!
- Say something, Osman!
My Osman! Come on!
Hurry up!
- Osman!
- Hurry up, Boran!
Hurry up!
Brother!
Go in!
Come on, valiants!
My Osman!
Brother!
- Brother!
- My Gündüz! Stop!
Stop! My Gündüz, stop!
We should let Selcan Hatun do her work.
Tell me the truth, Bamsı Bey!
What happened to my brother?
It was Sofia! We made it in time but
he was already wounded.
He was already wounded.
It looks serious, Bamsı Bey!
It is, Dündar Bey. But Selcan Hatun
and Bala will do what's necessary.
We shouldn't disturb them.
Son!
My Allah, take my other arm
but heal my Osman!
Save our Osman, my Allah...
Save our Osman...
Hold on, my Osman.
Hold on.
It's very deep.
What if searing it isn't enough?
What if it doesn't do?
What will we do then, mother?
What will we do without Osman?
Death is the only burden
that doesn't get better.
My Osman is alive. He's breathing.
My valiant will be okay.
He'll be okay.
Hold on, my valiant.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim
[in the name of Allah, the merciful and compassionate]
With the name of Allah!
Hold on, my Osman.
Stand still!
With the name of Allah!
Damn it!
Send some men to see if Osman returned
to his Tent or died in the forest.
- If he's alive, he'll attack the castle.
- As you order.
Call the knights in. Now!
Alexis!
Come here.
You'll go to our last hope of salvation.
To Aya Nichola. Tell him Sofia asks for
immediate support against the Turks.
As you order!
Aya Nichola? He'll never help us,
Princess. And you know th--
He will!
If this castle falls, the Christian unity
of these lands will fall with it.
Aya Nichola won't refuse this.
He's not okay.
We should be prepared for everything.
My Bey...
Gündüz!
My nephew!
Gündüz Bey!
- Gündüz.
- I can't leave my brother alone.
No. I can't leave my brother alone.
Mother...
What are you saying?
What would a wound do to my brother?
A single wound can't do
anything to my brother.
I can't leave him alone.
I can't. I--
My Gündüz, my child...
My girl Bala is taking care of my Osman.
There's always hope.
There's always hope, child.
I couldn't protect him.
I couldn't protect my brother, Bamsı Bey.
What will I say to my father?
Bamsı Bey?
You know these things.
What will I say to my father if he asks
what happened to Osman?
I couldn't protect him.
Child! My Osman will be okay!
He will be fine.
Don't worry. Calm down.
Stay strong.
Child! You're a Bey!
You must stand still so
the people can too!
You must be strong so we
can be too.
So we can be strong.
Be strong!
What will I say on the doomsday?
I couldn't support him like an uncle
because of my ambition.
I poked my nose into everything he did.
How can I say that I always pushed him
and tried to make him fail?
Don't blame yourself too much, my Dündar.
Don't. You made mistakes.
But everyone makes mistakes.
Isn't regretting the important thing?
Look, you've been on his side for
a long time.
Wouldn't Osman be mad at you if he
got up and heard what you're saying?
Wouldn't he be angry?
Wouldn't he be angry at you
because you were over those things?
What if he can't get up?
What if that valiant passes away?
What will I do then, Hazal?
How will I deal with this remorse?
Pull yourself together, Dündar Bey!
A valiant like Osman won't die so easily.
No. We will pray,
and Allah will heal him.
Don't drop your head. Osman will
get up the same way he always does.
You're like a father to him.
And he's like a son to you
Stand upright. So that he can be motivated
when he gets up and sees you!
You just wait. You'll draw your swords
and go into battles once again.
You'll support each other.
Inshallah.
Inshallah, Hatun.
I just want my Osman to
open his eyes...
...and tell me...
...''Get up, uncle...
...we are going to battle.''...
...and I will march before him.
I will be his shield. As long as...
...my nephew is healthy.
Göktuğ.
Your only legacy for me...
...was your loyalty for Osman Bey.
I came here with this loyalty, brother.
I swear to you...
...from now, we will live in one
body as two souls.
You will be with me...
... every time I swing my sword
against a heathen, brother.
You will be there.
Only the light of death can clean
my sins.
I won't wait long, brother.
I'll join you soon.
My heroic brother.
My Osman.
My valiant. I'm here.
I'm here, husband.
It will be over, Osman.
You will be well again. You'll be well.
Yes, yes, Osman?
Osman?
Open your eyes, Osman. Look at me.
Look at me. Look at me, Osman.
Open your eyes, my love.
Open it!
Look at me, Osman. Look at me!
Open your eyes! Look at me!
Gündüz Bey, help!
Help!
Osman, look at me, my valiant!
Look at me, my husband.
Osman, open your eyes!
Open your eyes, my love!
Osman! Osman!
Help!
Osman Bey! Osman Bey!
Osman Bey!
What's happening? What is this
rumble? What's happening.
We got news from Osman Bey, my Bey.
We should head there at once.
-Tell me what happened.
-Osman Bey...
What happened to Osman?
Tell me!
He ascended to heaven, my Beg.
My condolences.
Son...
What are you saying, son?
What are you saying?
My Bey.
Osman, Osman!
Osman!
My nephew! It's because of me...
It's because of me!
I couldn't stand behind him...
Dündar Bey, don't let yourself go.
It's because of me, it's my fault.
I couldn't stand behind him.
I couldn't stand behind my nephew.
Oh, my Osman.
It's my fault!
Osman!
My nephew!
Son...
Is it true, son?
Gündüz Bey.
People are waiting for
explanation.
My brother, Osman...
...is a mortal like every one of us.
And the end of every mortal is...
...leaving this world.
What is deathless is Allah.
Humans are mortal...
...and destined to vanish.
And time belongs to...
...Allah only.
Oh, Osman...
Oh, my nephew...
What will last forever is...
...the cause of Allah.
O valiant people of Kayıs!
Osmans,...
...Gündüzs,...
...Abdurrahman Ghazis...
...Borans and Ayazs...
...Bamsıs...
...are temporary.
What is constant is...
...the love of holy war...
...in our hearts.
Allahu Akbar! Allahu Akbar!
I've brought you an evangel,
princess.
Speak.
Osman Bey has died, your majesty.
Finally...
Jesus Christ, thank god.
We got rid of that wretched man
named Osman!
Hear it out!
Prepare the tables! Send the word
to every corner of the castle.
Osman kicked the bucket!
Now it's time for a feast!
Finally, it is over.
I avenged you, father.
Now you can rest in peace.
Thank god.
Forgive me, my Allah.
Aygül... Where is Aygül?
She was here, Saltukhan.
What are you looking at, fool?
Come on!
This lunatic will be trouble.
God damn it.
My dear father, the great man who
made me who I am...
For Yannis' brave soul!
Knights of Aya Nichola are coming.
Inform the princess.
The aid we were waiting from Aya Nichola
is here.
Aya Nichola, Lord of Inegol, sent his
brave men to our aid.
I raise my glass...
...for Osman's burning soul in hell!
Brave knights of Aya Nichola!
Welcome to our castle!
I see that Aya Nichola is as kind...
...as he is brave.
I'm sure that a chivalrous
lord such as Aya Nichola...
...sent a beautiful carpet
for our feet.
Who did this?
Osman son of Ertugrul Ghazi!
Osman...
My wolf-eyed brother, don't
let yourself down.
It's not the time to say goodbye.
Osman!
It's not the time I say goodbye.
Now it's time for conquest.
No one else other than Sheikh Edebali
and...
...my faithful friends...
...will know about our play.
Let them think...
...I am dead.
I've brought death upon your door, Sofia.
Soldiers, ambush!
Charge!
-Sofia!
-Stop him!
Stop him!
Wherever you run into, Sofia,
you can't outrun your death.
Now I will finish what I left
unfinished.
Come, then, Osman.
This castle will be your graveyard.
Attack, valiants!
Attack!
Ya Allah! With the name of Allah!
Fight, valiants!
Fight, dervishes!
-Come on!
-Come on, Gündüz!
Come on, warriors, come on!
Sofia! You have nowhere else
to go.
Every time I see this little wound,
I will remember you.
You won't be remembered by anyone.
I will banish you and your kind...
...to the damned steppes where
you came.
We came to clean these lands...
...which you polluted with
blasphemy.
Whatever you do...
...these lands will belong to Muslims.
Now it's time your time to answer
for your crimes.
That won't be as easy as you think, Osman.
Your evilness will have no profit for you,
Sofia.
The curse of god!
Damn Turk!
We Turks are the heat of Allah
against the cruels!
Sofia!
Stop Osman!
Princess.
Princess!
I won't give them even your body.
I will not!
Get her up!
Ya Allah!
Ya Fettah (one of Allah's qualities.)
Attack, my valiants, attack!
Brothers.
Brother.
Thank Allah who granted us...
...with this conquer.
Thank Allah.
From now on, Kulucahisar Castle is
muslim place.
Allah-u Akbar!
(Allah is the greatest!)
Inform the tent immediately.
Today, we conquer!
Today, Kayıs' feast day!
My relatives, my uncle, my friends...
- let them all come.
- Command is yours, my Bey
Mashaallah (praise be),
my valiant.
Don't be afraid.
Don't wince.
For the sake of Allah, who is the
creator of earth.
For the sake of our prophet
Muhammed Mustafa.
For the sake of his generation.
For the sake of one hundred and twenty
four thousand prophets.
I...
swear on my weapon...
Your goods, your life, your fatih,
your honor...
all are entrusted to us.
Come here.
Come.
The cruels saw Turks' heat.
Now, the opresseds shall see
our compassion.
Boran, reimburse these people.
Command is yours, my Bey.
Brothers!
- Bamsı Bey.
- Hey, my valiant!
Ey Masha Allah(praise be)
Masha Allah (praise be!) my valiant!
Well done!
Brother, brother.
Your pain is huge, my Bey.
You loved Osman as your son.
I lost another son of mine, Hatun.
Now, when I look back, I see that...
All of it is my fault.
Don't, Dündar Bey, it's not your fault.
Osman impressed us by his bravery.
He fought for his tent.
He became a martyr for the love of Allah.
It's not your fault. Don't act like that.
Son.
Your face is like a wet weekend.
What happened?
- Osman
- Yeah?
He didn't die.
He tricked us and Sofia to conquer the
castle, mother.
Do you hear what you are saying, son?
While we are weeping on his grave, he and
Gündüz, Bamsı Bey went to the castle.
They conquered the castle with their Alps.
This is such a time that we witness every
shape of evilness, Dündar Bey!
Here is the betrayal of your son who you
were weeping for.
He even avoids the castle from you.
Look what is your value in his eyes!
There's more, father.
Osman invites you to the castle.
He wants you to witness his victory.
An invitation...
needs to be accepted.
Yeah.
Go.
Don't let your father be alone, son.
Son.
Comprehend what betrayal is.
So that you don't end up like...
Batur, who was killed by Osman.
Those are non-muslims died in the war.
But you look at them pityingly.
What's the meaning of this, my Sheik?
You see them as dead non muslims.
When I look at them, I see unlucky people
that we couldn't teach.
Conquer is the first step of the
plane tree you saw in your dream, son.
Inshaallah, you will be the voice of
the oppressed.
Inshaallah, my Sheik, inshaallah.
- Our conquer shall be mubarak, Bey.
- Eyvallah Hatun (thank you)
He is İsa Sofu from our Yarens.
He came from Samarkand.
My relatives sent this Kayı
flag for you, Osman Bey.
This holy conquest is a fate.
Thanks to the valiants who are
of Yesevi descent...
and build prayer bridges between...
Söğüt and Samarkand.
Inshaallah, this flag...
will be flown
in more castles...
with the Ghazis, son.
Now, fly this flag...
in the castle you won with your weapons.
I think you've heard my Osman's victory?
That's why your eyes twinkle.
Did you know about Osman's game?
Why did you hide it from us?
-Do you know how to keep a secret?
-Yes, of course.
Come here.
My Osman knows it well.
Even his beard doesn't know
what he thinks.
Now, if you'll excuse me... We have a
victory feast tonight.
We have to prepare for it.
Is it done?
Is the duty done?
No.
She ran away.
What do you mean that Aygül ran away?
We looked everywhere.
But we couldn't find her.
We don't know where she is.
Hazal Hatun.
Why is Saltuk brother here?
Where is Aygül?
Mad girl.
She ran away.
You don't forgive...
betrayals, right?
You'll pay for..
what you did.
There's no excuse and compensation...
for betrayal.
He never had a suspicion
about me killing his son...
- and giving me his daughter.
- What did I do, Osman?
What did I do?
Forgiving cruels...
is a darkness for the innocent.
It's not right in our religion!
Betrayals are done, uncle.
Today is the day of victory.
Today...
is our day.
Allahu Akbar! Allahu Akbar!
(Allah is the greatest!)
Long live Osman Bey! Long live Osman Bey!
Allahu Akbar! Allahu Akbar!
(Allah is the greatest!)
Long live Osman Bey! Long live Osman Bey!
My Gündüz...
Thanks to my Allah that...
we saw this holy victory.
With your love of war, you'll
see more victories!
We'll conquer more
castles, Inshaallah Bamsı Bey!
Allahu Akbar! (Allah is the greatest!)
Don't worry, Hazal Hatun.
They'll find her.
She'll come back even if they can't.
Her problem is with me.
That's why she'll come back.
I don't worry about myself...
I'm afraid that my Dündar suffers again.
Aygül!
Burçin!
No!
Aygül!
Burçin!
Burçin...
Burçin... Burçin!
No!
My powerful and good comrades!
My friends...
My Alps...
We...
are the Kayı soldiers.
Both our aim and desire is...
the assent of Allah.
We came this land to spead the name
of Allah, and...
carry his real religion to everywhere!
Thank Allah who gives us strenght against
the cruels...
and put courage in our hearts!
Amin!
Brothers!
In the way of war, we have gone through
a lot of things.
We have made the impossible possible.
We faced so many things.
As long as we unite, nobody can
stand against us!
As long as we have this willing...
we will pave the way for a
lot of conquers!
Amin!
Friends!
In this way, some of our people fell...
Some of them became martyr...
I wish from Allah that...
The shining shahada of ours shall be
light for the generation of Muhammed!
Amin.
The bodies we buried here...
shall be courage for our valiants!
Amin!
My my Lord make us victorious!
- make us fair!
- Amin!
- make us compassionate!
make us so strong that...
we shall defeat the cruels
with our strenght from our Lord.
Amin!
My valiants!
We shall not stop!
The sky is our home, sun is our flag...
in the power of our faith!
Our swords will echo from Nikea
to Prussia!
Our voices will be nightmare in
Constantine!
Because our love is blessed...
and our aim is found
the eternal state!
Our words are for the world!
Forever justice! Forever freedom!
- Allahu Akbar! (Allah is the greatest!)
- Allahu Akbar!
Allahu Akbar! (Allah is the greatest!)
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim. (in the name of Allah, the merciful and compassionate.)
You can recite the azan.
"Allah is greater."
"I bear witness that there is
no deity but Allah."
"I bear witness that Muhammad is
the Messenger of Allah."
"I bear witness that Muhammad
is the Messenger of Allah."
"Hasten to the prayer (Salah)."
"Hasten to the salvation."
"Allah is greater..."
"There is no deity but Allah."
There is no deity but Allah.
Please contact turkision@gmail.com
for any inquiries